(Sheldon:)I am. So much so that
I'm gonna bring her here
(Sheldon:)for dinner on our next date night.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Raj:)So, in the last 20 minutes,
(Raj:)we've seen a crazy woman
kissing a fetus in a jar.
(Raj:)We've seen a guy cut in half
and sewn to a fish.
(Howard:)And the brutal dismemberment
of a rotisserie chicken by my mother.
(Raj:)On the bright side,
she didn't even notice the pill.
(Raj:)Why does Emily like this stuff?
(Raj:)Do you think there's something
psychologically wrong with her?
(Howard:)-What difference does it make?
-What do you mean?
(Howard:)Oh, come on, she could
have a freezer full
(Howard:)of ex-boyfriend's body parts
and you'd still go out with her.
(Raj:)I do like that the ex-boyfriend's
out of the picture.